And in breaking news,
it's been confirmed that last week's devastation
was caused by the legendary Demon Bull King.
Questions still remains about the small
overpowered young man who saved us all.
Authorities warn citizens on...
And I was like, "Stop there, Demon Bull King."
And D.B.K.'s all like, "You can't stop me! I'm crazy!"
And then I grabbed my staff, and woosh! I created this giant mech!
Uh oh, looks like you sprung a leak, MK.
Oh jeez!
I've just pulled a quadruple shift at the shop.
And I show up to see you've all been slacking off all day!
Oh, Piggy, relax.
A little time off never hurt anyone.
Yeah! A time off never hurt nobody.
Look out!
(scream)
Huh?
Kid!
I…am…invincible!
Yeah!
Look, MK,
just 'cause you got the Monkey King's powers and all, It don't mean-
(Gasps.)
MK! How about…
this?
I... am... invincible!
(Sighs.) Look, kiddo,
you're a superhero now. You're going to need-
A cape! Maybe a logo, or a headquarters!
Some vehicles, you know, all the stuff to help you beat bad guys!
No, what I was getting at was-
To the Sea-Crate…Base!
Welcome…to our new team base!
Mei, when did you make this?
How did you make this?
Say, Sandy,
weren't you building a secret base for MK, too?
Umm…no.
An eon trapped under a mountain and now this?
I had the staff in my grasp.
I should have crushed the thief when I had the chance!
Oh, my love. Don't be so dramatic.
We've nothing but time. You will bring the world to its knees.
And sooner than you think, Father.
Allow me to secure the power you desire.
Get it done then.
I won't fail you again.
Welcome to the Weather Station, where you'll notice it's another beautiful day.
Here at the Weather Station, we control the city's weather to bring you a perfect day every day.
Uh yeah, hey kid, I'd like to help you and your friends, but I'm pretty busy.
Not for much longer.
Citizens. It is I, Red Son.
I have taken control of the Weather Station and will harness the very power of nature to return my father to his former glory.
This message is more of a courtesy really.
(laugh)
When I'm finished, my father will once more dominate the world! And then-
Oh look! A lightning button.
Oh yeah!
What do you mean "Oh yeah"?
This ain't an "oh yeah" moment!
Chill out, Pigsy. I'm invincible, remember?
If he wants to tussle with the champ, then I say bring it!
Yeah! 'Cause he's a superhero, yo! The Red Baby is gonna get M.K.O'd!
Uh, you got a lot to learn, kid.
Don't just dive head first in the danger-
Wait, what did I just say?
(Laughs.) Totally invincible!
Not so fast, Red Son!
Noodle Boy! I thought I smelt some garbage!
Turns out I was right!
(Laughs.)
You're laughing now, but…I'm invincible!
So yeah, you're basically toast.
Prepare to get M.K.O'd!
Yeah, MK! You show him who's bo- Aaaaaah!
Ah! Jeez, watch what'cha doing!
Ah! Sorry, Mei!
Oh, my chakra!
Oh, no! You've killed him!
Eh, he's a big guy. He'll be fine.
You dorks done beating each other up yet?
Yes, and you're next on my list!
I guess the garbage takes itself out now! (he laughs.)
(screams)
[car alarms]
How you doing there, bud?
Monkey King! Great!
Now that you're here, we can go fly up there and smash that-
No, no, no, no, no.
In case you forgot, I'm retired.
You're supposed to be taking care of the bad guys.
Besides, you're invincible! Right?
Well, yeah I mean, I am invincible, but, you know.
Every time I try to do anything I just gunk everything up.
Something's wrong.
Hey, what are you doing?
Oh yeah, you're right.
Oh, this is bad. Something's really wrong!
[Gasps] What is it? What's wrong?
It's you, dummy.
What?
In order to have full control of your powers, you need self-confidence.
I got self-confidence.
No, you're just loud.
The only way to get self-confidence is-
Fake it 'til I make it?
No! Practice!
You think I took shortcuts? No.
It took me centuries of training and fighting and just beating up demons.
Just, so many demons.
A-anyway, nothing worth anything comes for free.
But what about my friends, the city?
They're all counting on me.
(Groans.) Fine. If it'll stop your whining.
I know a way to limit your powers so you can learn to control them. But...
But what?
You won't be invincible anymore.
(he sighs)
Alright let's do it
All right. No turning back.
Feeling alright, bud?
Yeah.
(he laughs) Peasants.
Oh, Red Son!
Let's settle this for real. I won't let you get away with this.
Ha! You're back to beat yourself up some more?
Hey. I'll have you know I can control my powers now.
Only downside is I'm not invincible anymore, so, I could die.
What?!
Forgot I said that I got this.
Here comes Monkie Kid!
(Screams) I totally don't got this!
How am I supposed to fight all of them?
Oh! It's that weird Gold Vision thingy.
That's it! Oh!
Not so tough without all your Monkey King powers, are you?
Oh, look! A lighting button.
(wobbling sound)
You may have won this round but... you're still garbage.
Let's get this place back to normal
And that should do it.
MK!
Aww, you really did limit your powers.
Yeah. Just till I learn to control them better.
And... how are you gonna do that?
Practice, practice, practice.
(Mei, Pigsy, Sandy and Tang all laugh.)
(screams)
The little thief has stolen from me again!
I will not be undone by an insect!
(whispers, overlapping) You must do what I say.
Now, that is power.
Power.