OFFSHORE
presents
With the participation of the
National Center of Cinema and Animated Picture
Help for the production program
With the support of
the Occitanie Region
in partnership with
the National Center of Cinematography
A movie by
Your turn.
The ideal time is 45 seconds, okay?
Well, you'll take some day to
get used to it, that's normal.
No but I just did this one, go to the one beside.
Your product!
Annouk, that's the third time, heh.
No but don't hesitate to do that, yeah?
I really need this job.
Everyone needs it here.
Lola!
Would you mind helping Florence,
she's struggling because of her back.
Yeah, yeah, don't worry.
It's not a problem for the baby?
Oh no, it's not even been three months, so...
I'll go do the trash, you can take the cart.
Oh thank you, love.
You're welcome.
It's just that it would be good to tell them for...
We're not at their disposal.
When the boat arrives late, they have to pay us
for the delay, fuck.
Because the ones they rehire the next morning...
No, listen, I'll talk about it to Bernal, okay?
- You already said that last week.
- No, promise.
That's good for the baby?
It didn't kill the two others.
Why did you took back the cart,
what is Florence doing?
Don't know, she wanted to redo the showers?
- Want some?
- No, thank you.
You saw Melvin's choreography just before?
I had to leave before the end.
Ah, it was so good.
But it's sure he's the one who will win.
On top of that he's supra handsome.
I think they're fucking with Angie.
They're too connected, it's impossible.
However the one I don't like is the chick on the jury.
What's her name again?
Hum, Marie-France.
Marie-France...
She scores like a mess...
Huuu your fingers are dead at the tip of your hands.
Oh huu, think about the piano here,
you need to vibrate the air around you.
It means nothing.
Heh, why don't we try?
Like that the hand, they do like that.
Fuck, Mylène, there's a problem
come quick!
What, what is it?
Happy birthday to you,
happy birthday to you,
happy birthday to you, Mylène,
happy birthday to you!
But how did you do that?
Special authorization from Bernal!
Heh, it's useful you caught his eye.
Vodka!
Cheers, Mylène.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Lola.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You have the 10 euros for the gift?
Hum, I had to pay for Mattéo's canteen,
I'm a little under water here,
but I promise, next week...
- But hum, you think I'm not under water?
I don't know, ten euros it's-
it's a week of food for the kids.
And I'm not just getting out of my divorce.
And Karine? She couldn't take care of it herself?
You want some cake?
Karine, now.
No but don't worry, we have half an hour, there aren't many cabins,
tonight it's a party!
We're all good.
Happy birthday from all of us!
Oh, thank you. Thank you so much.
Dance classes
Card/Gift
Joseph Fontaine
Dance classes
Card/Gift
This gift card is for:
Joseph Fontaine
You're alright?
Yes, coming.
Come, we'll take a picture!
Come on, come!
Yes of course, I-I- I'll tell them
right away to come back to work.
Yes, thank you very much.
Yes, a real surprise, yes.
Yes, of course.
Yes, sorry hum, no, excuse me,
we need to get back to it, the ferry leaves in an hour.
Your back feels better?
- Thanks for the gift.
- Hey, got the flu.
This one, the second she can slack off...
By the way, wh- who had the idea?
What do you mean?
Well, you annoyed us so much with Dancing with the Stars
when we came to eat at your place...
So we all thought about it, right away.
Well let's go.
I'll help you get everyone back to work.
Won't be a piece of cake.
And the new one here, a bit dim,
hm, I'll take care of it.
it's your party after all.
Sorry.
Can't you lower the volume a bit?
Won't you rather have a drink?
Florence told me you were the one to buy the gift?
Danse ofr fuck off, got it?
- Hey, wait a bit, we can hear your music...
Where do you come from, who are you?
Come one, come one, bug off!
Come on, end of the party, back to work!
There's 40 cabins left
and the boat leaves in 45 minutes.
So, we can take turns, but I don't have enough people at the front.
But 45 minutes of what?
It's been three time this week that those fucking shitty english
have a two hours delay,
and we're not even compensated.
And they don't care, they don't give a damn!
I'm sorry Mylène, but tonight is saturday night
and we all want to party.
For once Mylène. For once!
Shit.
You're good?
It will pass.
Anyway, thank you.
It's nice of you to take care of me.
I'll bring something to clean that.
Is it you?
What?
The one who bought the gift, it's you?
Well, it's all of us, why?
But who took care of it?
What do you mean?
Who ordered it? Who wrote on the voucher?
Florence took care of that.
But why, you don't like it?
She noticed the trophy on the TV,
she thought you would like it.
You prefer salsa?
And tonight we won't move from the boat.
Like that they might understand that their fucking delay-
I had the idea for the tango, but if you prefer something else...
What's wrong, hey, get off me!
I know you're the one who wrote on the gift.
Fuck, you're fucking annoying.
What do you want?
I want your post.
Your post.
Where is Mylène?
Good evening, Mister Bernal.
I don't know where she is, but anyway, we, are here.
But the boat is about to leave.
But we're staying, in exchange for
all the hours you owe us.
The other when we went to eat at your place,
I found that funny, that trophy under the TV.
So I looked.
Then I thought it must've been typo.
This "J", might belong to someone else.
Then it bothered me.
And now with internet you can find anything.
We've been waiting to be compensated for the delays for months.
I already reported it above, just wait.
Yeah, that's waht you say each week.
Each week it's the same crap.
Ok, ok Karine.
It's not against you,
I really need this post.
Bernal will never agree.
You just have to tell him, you explain that you don't want to do that anymore!
You think he'll be happy to know he's hitting on a tranny?
Because all that is just fake.
It's a lie, a deception.
Huh? Joseph!
Let's go! Everybody out. We're evacuating ship, party's over.
No one move! Tonight, we'll also go to England!
It's a mess, [intelligible], you can';t handle it no more.
If you don't go, I'll spill it all.
Hey, come, it's a party, let's dance.
Wait.
Do whatever.
Translated by Lupin Traduction