Hello everyone! It's your friendly neighborhood lotus!
Because I kept using stand-ins for zoom classes,
Da-shi finally caught me.
I can only record this video
in my lotus root form.
Do not worry,
Da-shi will turn me back as soon as fae calms down.
What should I do to make fae less angry?
Yangwen: Sheep's Language, homonym for "Foreign Language" i.e. English.
This isn't my style.
Oh yes!
I can make Da-shi a little statue.
Dangerous behaviour!
Humans do not imitate!
Complete.
I think Da-shi will be very happy
when fae receives this.
This is the end of this video.
Next time we meet I will be in my regualr form again.
Memes made from this video
can be downloaded by searching "Fei Ren Zai Lotus"